福勒探员 请进
Special agent Fowler, please come in.
为什么列兵戴利会在那里摄像？
What's private Daley doing here with that camera?
他将为今天的会话做记录
He will be making a record of today's session.
士兵 太近了
Soldier... too close.
很抱歉我的穿着不合场合
Sorry I didn't dress for the occasion.
与平时一样就好 比尔
Formality won't be any more necessary than usual, Bill.
但我不得不通知你\N我们的上司已经做好了战争准备
But I do need to inform you that our higher-ups are on the war path.
他们得明白最近事件发生的原委
They want answers regarding recent events.
或许我们应该从擎天柱的死亡开始
Perhaps we should begin with the demise of Optimus Prime.
我以为我们已经讨论过了！
I thought we've straightened all this out.
擎天柱现在活得很好
Prime is alive and well.
这对高层来说很难接受
That's difficult for our superiors to accept
除非能看到擎天柱和他的仿冒品
without the benefit of seeing Optimus and the alleged imposter.
看到他们两个站在一起？目前看来是不行了
Side by side? That didn't seem to be the wisest option at the time.
空军接到直接命令 一旦发现任何汽车人 立即摧毁
The sky jockeys were under direct orders to destroy any and all Autobots on sight.
我们现在在高度戒备状态
We were in a heightened state of security.
来说说好消息
Let's consider the positives.
现在我们掌握了关于机械党的更多情报
We now possess greater intel regarding M.E.C.H..
尤其是他们的匪首 塞拉斯
Particularly their leader, Silas.
真名是莱兰・毕晓普 上校 前特种战术部队成员
the stage name of one Colonel Leland Bishop, ex-special tactics.
主导设计了达摩克利斯计划
The architect of project Damocles.
通过卫星激光束 攻击地球上的任意目标
Satellites in orbit firing laser beams at any target on Earth.
很早以前就废止了
Long since mothballed
这也是毕晓普叛逃的主要原因
and the primary reason for Bishop's discharge.
叛逃之后 他更肆无忌惮地\N重拾曾经放弃的其他疯狂计划
He had other wild ideas, which he practiced with even greater abandon once he went rogue.
现在仍没有找到他的尸体
And still, no sign of his remains.
更令人担心的是
Of greater concern
塞拉斯的手下可能也是特战成员
M.E.C.H. agents, like Silas, might also be special tactics.
难道是现役人员？
As in, currently enlisted?
所以他们要把脸蒙上
One obvious motive for hiding their faces.
我想申请继续深入调查
I would urge a thorough investigation
而我们的金属大手朋友在这方面要远远胜于我们
and leave bigger threats to metal hands more capable than our own.
因为你被批准进行如此高度机密的任务
Because you've been allowed to operate at these deeply classified levels
所以或许我们需要你提供背景资料
perhaps you could provide some background.
我们的变形朋友是有着自主意识的机械生命体
Our transforming visitors are autonomous, robotic organisms
来自塞博特恩星球 他们曾经历了一场战争
from the planet Cybertron. They were fighting a war.
核心问题 是为了我们的世界对于能量的控制权
Foremost, over control of our world's supply of Energon
也就是汽车人以及霸天虎的生命能量
the fuel and lifeblood of all Autobots and Decepticons alike.
你还记得战争的末期吗？
Do you recall the period late in the war
双方都把找到的能量藏在外星球
when both sides began hiding their Energon spoils off-world?
当然记得 所以在这样的星球上会有能量矿
Of course, it's the reason Energon deposits exist on planets such as this one.
正是如此 这样的星球上才会有战争
It is also the reason battles came to be waged on planets such as this one.
这场争夺能量和黑暗能量的战争 延续至今
These battles over Energon, and its dark counterpart, continue to this day.
你对这些确信吗？
And you know this for certain?
我的所见不但使我信服
I've seen more than enough to make me a believer.
我还通过擎天柱的队伍获取战场情报
But I rely upon field reports from team Prime
然后再共享给你
which I, in turn, share with you.
能跳过这些吗？
Skip ahead, if you would
直接叙述你所参与的部分 福勒探员
to the history of your involvement, Agent Fowler.
你也知道 我刚开始并不喜欢这项看管汽车人的工作
As you know, I wasn't overjoyed with what I assumed was gonna be a bot-sitting assignment.
擎天柱！
Prime!
等等 别告诉我你们在办托儿所吗？
Wait. Don't tell me. He's out pancaking a mini-mall.
然而我发现这项工作的危险系数过于惊人
But its occupational hazards turned out to be surprisingly severe.
把能量棍拿来…
Bring the prod.
另外汽车人也无数次挽救了我的生命
And, by now, the bots have saved my bacon more times than I can count.
当然 我也投桃报李 还了一些人情
Of course, I've returned the favor a time or two...
随叫随到 伙计 着地支援这就来
Any time, fella. Ground floor's coming fast.
有时需要利用下职权
... sometimes exercising my authority...
这女孩我带走
The girl comes with me.
有时需要依靠敏捷的思维
... sometimes relying upon quick thinking.
我们就是…校准了一下系统 我们还…
We were just... calibrating the subsystems, and we, uh
有点小问题 但现在好了
had a... surge.  But it's fine now.
你那边好吗？
How are you?
我也犯过一些错
And I've made a few mistakes.
啊！又来这套！
Ah! Not again!
啊 又是这套把戏！
Ah! Not this again!
福勒探员 能逐一介绍一下他们吗？
If you would, Agent Fowler, provide a roll call.
要是碰巧遇上 我们好分清张三李四？
So, we'll know who's who in the event of another bot snaps?
没错
Something like that.
好吧那么…
Well, there's...
隔板
Bulkhead.
你是一辆车？
Are you a car?
我敢说你是卡车 是大脚车！
I bet you're a truck ... a monster truck!
你喜欢重金属音乐吗？你多重？
Do you like heavy metal? How much do you weigh?
用破碎锤打过沙包吗？
Ever use a wrecking ball for a punching bag?
听着 神子 我在成为战士之前 是个工人
Look, Miko, before I became a warrior, I was a laborer
建筑工 我能造东西 也能拆东西
-- nstruction. I can build stuff. I can break stuff.
可别的都不会
And that's it.
当然我跟这个大块头并不很投缘
Of course, big foot and I don't always see eye to eye.
别用那个电话 它…
Don't use that phone. It's...
坏了
out of order.
他不是最敏捷的汽车人
He may not be the most agile bot...
别往下看
Don't look down.
他也是最不可能成为科学家的一个
And he's the first to admit he's no rocket scientist.
拜托 医生 没什么好检查的
Come on, Doc. There's nothing up there to scan.
把频道调回去 我想看完这整场节目
Switch it back! I want to see the hoedown showdown!
但他的蛮力是无价之宝
But his brute strength is invaluable.
所幸救护车是技术领域的专家
Thankfully, the science angle is more than covered by Ratchet.
医官他比较…严谨
The Doc can be a little... tightly wound.
你们也想做到最好吧？
Without my supervision?!
那就欣赏大师的手笔吧！
You want them to be right, don't you?
控制狂
Control freak.
但当需要他战斗时也毫不含糊
But he brings his "A" game when the situation calls for it.
没事了
It's all right.
我是一辆救护车
I'm an emergency vehicle.
还有阿尔茜
Then there's Arcee.
那辆摩托车？
The motorcycle?
不要被那小巧的身材所迷惑
Don't be fooled by the smaller footprint.
她很厉害
She leaves a mark.
大黄蜂是队伍中的侦察兵
Bumblebee's the team scout.
但要我说 这个还在培训中的战士比看上去要成熟
But the warrior-in-training seems pretty accomplished, if you ask me.
阿尔茜可以说是少言寡语了
Arcee may be a bot of few words
而大黄蜂更是完全不能说话…
but Bumblebee doesn't use any...
…说了我们也听不懂
... that we can understand.
它…想让我们上车
I-It wants us to get in.
不 就我一个
No, just me.
你怎知道的？
How do you know that?
它就是这么说的
It said so.
这跟他的一段经历有关
Turns out it's with good reason.
在塞博特恩的战争中
During the war for Cybertron
这个可怜的孩子被威震天损毁了发声器
the poor kid got his voice box torn out by Megatron.
所以汽车人并非如我们所想的那般坚不可摧
So, the Autobots aren't quite the indestructible war machines we'd hoped.
不要误会 他们具有很强的抗击打能力
Don't misunderstand. They can take serious punishment.
但他们确实有弱点
But they do have their... vulnerabilities.
你刚刚像小女孩一样尖叫了吗？
Did you just scream like a little girl?
没有 或许吧
No! Maybe...
这或许不是我们意料中的结局
This may not be the finish that we had planned
但如果真要在这里结束
but if this is indeed the end
如果我们要和火种源融为一体…
if we are to become one with the Allspark...
不！飞过山的生命信号…
No. Cliffjumper's life signal
刚刚消失了
just went offline.
站在这儿哭是不会让他复生的
If Cliff's gone, standing around here sulking won't bring him back.
我们曾经在失去飞过山时悲痛地认识到了这一点
We learned that the hard way when we lost Cliffjumper.
根据你的报告 飞过山是上一个阵亡的汽车人？
And, for the record, Cliffjumper was the last Autobot casualty?
我告诉过你 你缴获的那个无生命的汽车人不是擎天柱
I told you. The lifeless Autobot you have in storage isn't Prime.
那是个冒牌货
It's a Knockoff!
我们只是听了你的一面之词
We have only your word to go on
并没有发现塞拉斯的踪迹
without any trace of Silas
也没有证据表明他掌握了复制和遥控技术
or the alleged technology M.E.C.H. utilized to control said Knockoff.
清除一切痕迹是机械党的处事方法
A clean scrub is M.E.C.H.'s M.O.
你和我都了解这点！
You and I both know it!
你最后的报告中称擎天柱加入了霸天虎！
Your last debriefing indicated that Optimus Prime had joined the Decepticons.
那不是他自愿的！擎天柱失忆了
Not willfully! Prime had amnesia.
我以为我已经说得很清楚了！
I know I was clear on that.
但你要明白我们的外部观察员\N可以把这个与最近军事基地的遇袭联系起来
But you can see where outside observers might connect the dots to the recent attack on our base.
比尔 五星上将们很担心
Bill, the five-stars have grown
我们信任的这些生命体 一旦反目
nervous that we've been placing our trust in beings who could so easily inflict harm
能轻而易举地伤害我们
if they chose to turn on us.
因此我接到命令来审查你
That's why I've been asked to determine
决定是否交付军事法庭
whether I should bring you before a tribunal.
军事法庭？他们会停止整个行动！
Tribunal? They could shut down our operation
把我关进监狱！
put me in jail.
布莱斯将军 擎天柱不是莽撞的人！
General Bryce, Prime is no loose cannon.
他绝对不是！
He's anything but.
汽车人虽然很巨大 但他们行动很谨慎
The bots may be big, but they watch where they step.
哪怕是孩子们…
Heck, even the kids...
孩子们？
Kids?
啊 哈哈 我们是这样称呼我们的…
Ah... that's what we call our...
…室内预备队的
"in-house support team".
我不知道除了你以外
I wasn't aware you were utilizing any of our resources other than yourself.
他们不是…现役军人
They're... not enlisted.
你让平民涉入军事机密行动？
You've involved civilians in a classified operation?
他们是优秀的人才 在…
Highly accomplished civilians who contribute specialized expertise in...
计算机 医学 以及…沟通交流方面有杰出的贡献
computer science... medicine... uh... communications.
我喜欢拆东西！
I love breaking stuff!
变态！
Twisted.
把心脏带回来
Bring the hurt!
书呆子又来了
Nerd alert.
僵尸！
Zombie!
是从外太空降临的 太厉害了…
Smackdown in outer space. That was cool.
那么他们会服从命令吧
So, they know how to take orders.
可以…这么说吧
You... could... say that.
欢迎光临KO快餐厅 每个肉饼都顶呱呱
Welcome to K.O. Drive-In, where every patty's a Knockout.
您想要点什么？
May I take your order?
但是他们打破常规思维去解决问题的方式
But while they lack in military discipline
完全足以弥补缺乏军事训练的不足
they more than make up for with outside-the-box problem-solving.
唉 没声音
Nothing.
天哪 谁想得到
Gee, imagine that.
四维空间的手机信号这么差
The fourth dimension has lousy cellphone reception.
嘿 伙计们…电话响了
Wait, guys, guys, guys. The phone... rang.
说明有信号
We're getting a signal.
汽车人看不见也听不见我们 可能是因为…
Maybe the Autobots can't see or hear us because...
我们也许在做超高速运动
we're moving at hyperspeed or something.
他们勇气可嘉
Their courage is to be admired.
把他按住！
Hold him still!
他们一次又一次的证明了
They've proven, time and again
他们为了自己的国家
that they're willing to put their lives on the line for their country...
自己的星球甘愿牺牲
and their planet.
因此你的平民队员与敌人有过接触
So, your civilians have made enemy contact.
我对面孔过目不忘 人类的也算上
I never forget a face... even that of a human.
你要是敢骗人
You double-cross anyone
我让你永远忘不了我这张脸 给我记住！
mine is the face you'll never forget! Never!
基本上 他们什么都见识过了…
They've... pretty much seen it all.
神子 别看！
Miko, look away!
- 但…\N- 把头扭过去！
- But...\N- Turn your head away!
但是请放心 汽车人重视这些人类――
Rest assured, the safety of these humans... of all humans...
甚至是所有人类――的生命安全
remains the primary concern of the Autobots.
他们没有防护罩！
They have no protective shell.
如果不小心被踩到 他们就…扁了
If they get underfoot, they will go... squish.
那么从现在起 救护车
Then, for the time being, Ratchet
我们必须走一步 看一步
we must watch where we step.
并且我们的同伴也不会改变这个立场
And our colleagues wouldn't have it any other way.
这儿对我来说就像天堂一样
I'm living a dream here in bots' "wanna".
你们谁都别想破坏我的美梦！
And I will not allow you or anyone else to shatter it!
他们同汽车人建立了深厚的羁绊
They've forged meaningful bonds with the bots.
阿尔茜呢？
Where's Arcee?
你干脆跟她结婚好了
Why don't you just marry her?!
我就在你后面
I'm right behind you.
在我忙于做其他事时
And they provide valuable assistance whenever
他们为汽车人提供了可贵的帮助
I'm otherwise engaged in the field.
这是威廉・福勒特工的电话号码
You've reached special Agent William Fowler.
我正在进行秘密强化训练
I'm currently on an intensive training retreat
周二之前不会回来
and unavailable until Tuesday.
我讨厌跟机器说话
I hate talking to machines.
他们参与的所有行动
But their involvement was never intended to be
都是经过人道主义考量的
anything other than humanitarian...
通过他们 汽车人对地球上的生命加深了了解
to provide the Autobots with the means of better understanding life on our planet.
侦察兵应该能杀人于无形
A scout should be silent but deadly.
怎么？
What?
可能还要装一个小东西
Maybe it needs one of these doohickeys.
你是摩托车 阿尔茜
You're a motorcycle, Arcee.
你难道不会制造摩托发动机吗？
Shouldn't you know how to build a motorcycle engine?
你还是人类呢 杰克 你能造出小肠来吗？
You're a human, Jack. Can you build me a small intestine?
你们要传送的地方 不光是密闭空间
You want me to not only bridge you into a confined space
而且移动速度每小时140多公里！
but one traveling at 90 miles per hour?!
我根本无法想象可能出现的意外
I can't even count the number of ways that can go wrong...
大面积错位损伤 四肢骨折 金属烧伤
mass displacement, trauma, twisted limbs, metal burn.
呃 也许没有最后那种
Well, maybe not the last one.
不过 他们的很多科学技术我们都还没学到
Sadly, we haven't begun to take full advantage of their science.
比如 我可以不穿航空服驾驶垂直起降战机
I mean, I can pilot my v-tol without ever having to wear a flight suit.
你的内脏不会爆炸吗？
What keeps your organs from exploding?
救护车对机舱内的调压器做了改进
A modification Ratchet performed on the cabin-pressure regulator.
我…喜欢舒服一些
I like to be comfortable.
…有些跑题了
We... may be getting off track.
请你说明为什么威震天的项上人头还未被献上？
Please address why we haven't yet been served Megatron's steel head on a silver platter.
不…
No!
霸天虎头目的生命力极其顽强…答案简单明了
The leader of the Decepticons has nine lives, plain and simple.
可我看见的确实是他
Well, I'm staring right at him.
好消息是 威震天没有回应我的目光
Good news is, Megatron isn't exactly staring back.
我们并非没有尝试过
It's not like we haven't tried.
糟糕的是
The sick part is
当我们能干掉他的时候 我们需要他
the moment we might have pulled it off, we needed him.
威震天事实上帮助过我们拯救了全人类
Megatron actually helped us save humanity.
擎天柱 我们过去的阵营 什么汽车人 霸天虎
Optimus, our past alliances... Autobot, Decepticon...
都去他的吧 眼下 宇宙大帝复活了
no longer matter... not while Unicron lives.
请解释
Elaborate.
我们遇到了一个比机械党和霸天虎更具威胁的敌人
We found ourselves facing an even greater threat than M.E.C.H. or the Decepticons.
就在地球内部 字面上的内部
Literally an enemy within...
宇宙大帝…我知道这听起来很疯狂 不过我要是告诉你
Unicron. I know this is gonna sound crazy, but what if I told you
地球的核心跟科学理论的解释完全不同时
our planet's core isn't made up of what science has led us to believe it is?
福勒探员 看来我得中止这次会谈 让你先接受心理评估
Agent Fowler, I'm sorry to say I'm forced to discontinue this debriefing until you undergo a full psychological evaluation.
你是认真的吗？
Seriously?
作为美国政府的代表
As a representative of the United States Government
我认为你心智不大正常
I believe that you may have lost your sanity.
布莱斯将军 我向你保证我神志清醒
General Bryce, I assure you that I am quite sane.
此事与逻辑完全相悖 比尔 黑暗能量？
It defies all logic, Bill. Dark Energon?
然后又当着笔录员说
Then you go on record saying that you believe in
你相信头上长角的魔马？
magical horses with horns on their heads.
什么？
What?
你不是报告说 威震天协助打败了独角兽吗？
Do you deny previously reporting that Megatron helped defeat a Unicorn?
你以为…
That's what you...
宇宙―大帝！终极恶魔！
Unicron! The ultimate evil!
请划掉这一段
Permission to strike this from the record.
批准 不过警告你注意言辞
Granted. But consider yourself on notice.
你说过 威震天一度与我们联手
You were saying. Megatron proved to be an ally.
这种情况很罕见
The circumstances were unique.
相反 霸天虎中最有可能为我们所用的是红蜘蛛
Oddly, the 'con most likely to be of service is Starscream...
这只是权宜之计
only be default...
因为他对他自己的同伴的仇视 比对我们还深
because he may despise his team more than he despises ours.
不 主人！
No, master!
红蜘蛛在威震天面前一直三心二意
Starscream's loyalty to Megatron has always been questionable.
如果他真的和霸天虎决裂
If he has truly split from the Decepticons
这个了解军情的俘虏 也许是个值得结交的盟友
our prisoner's knowledge of their agendas could make him a valuable ally.
威震天不念旧情 想把我干掉
Megatron tried to extinguish my Spark in cold blood!
还有那个一心想取代我的混蛋毒蜘蛛
Then all that replaced me with that traitorous wretch, Arachnid.
她竟然丢下我不管！让我自生自灭！
She abandoned me! Left me for scrap!
所以 干嘛不过河拆桥呢？
So why not rat them out?
然而即便威震天一度试图处决他
But even after Megatron attempted to terminate him
红蜘蛛仍然试图赢得主人的欢心
Starscream still tried to win his master's faith.
威震天该对我刮目相看 我不光救了他
Imagine Megatron's appreciation when I not only rescue him
还抓了个汽车人
but deliver an Autobot.
那样一来 我就可以重振雄风了
I believe that would restore my stature quite nicely.
由于缺乏安全感 红蜘蛛比威震天更难以捉摸
Starscream's insecurity is what makes him less predictable than Megatron.
某种程度上 甚至更加危险…
And in some ways, even more dangerous.
我说的话就是圣旨 这儿我说了算！
I make the decisions here. I am in charge!
他真该分清楚自己到底是想要取代威震天 还是要在威震天面前得宠
He really needs to figure out if it's Megatron's job he wants or Megatron's approval.
我又要追问一下
I must, in turn, ask why successful termination of Starscream
为什么红蜘蛛还未被成功消灭？
has not been achieved.
空中优势一直使得虎子们占尽上风
Air superiority continues to provide the 'Cons with the upper hand.
个别时候 我们也能挫伤对方
though we manage to inflict the occasional setback.
但难以逆转劣势
But the fact remains...
红蜘蛛落跑以后 为我们提供了宝贵的情报
Starscream has supplied valuable intel since he went rogue.
我得到了关于你们领袖的情报
Starscream: "I have obtained information regarding your leader.
带上医疗箱
Bring medical kit."
不用担心 汽车人不会盲目地听信他
Not to worry. The bots know better than to trust him implicitly.
再靠近一步 就把你的小器官变成废铁
One step and your previous biomech is scrap.
幸运的是 尽管战略眼光独到
Fortunately for us, despite his strategic brilliance
红蜘蛛最大的敌人就是他自己
Starscream is his own worst enemy.
嗯 什么？
What?
呃 我的变形齿轮！
My T-cog!
你飞不起来了？
You're grounded?
他也不是唯一叛离威震天的人
And he isn't the only one who's taken flight from Megatron.
那只蜘蛛？
The spider.
毒蜘蛛 生性残忍
Airachnid, as sadistic as they come.
她和阿尔茜有着很深的过节
And she and Arcee have quite a history.
我总觉得
I can't help but feel the next time
下一次她们将战个你死我活
they lock horns, only one's gonna walk away.
除非威震天先找到毒蜘蛛
Unless Megatron gets to Airachnid first.
所以说霸天虎的内斗一直不断？
So, the infighting among the Decepticon ranks continues.
不仅如此 威震天看似无法团结他的核心集团
And then some. Megatron can't seem to keep his inner circle holding hands.
你不认为我们能利用霸天虎的内斗吗
And you don't think we could take advantage of the chaos?
说服霸天虎投诚？
Motivate a Decepticon to join our cause?
有一名霸天虎受到擎天柱的尊敬
There is one whom Prime seems to respect.
尽管霸天虎改邪归正的可能性不大
While it is unlikely that any Decepticon will choose the path of good
但他们毕竟有改变命运的潜力
even they possess the potential for change.
但在目击骇翼夷平一座小镇后
But having witnessed Dreadwing tear up a town
我对他已不抱任何希望
I wouldn't hang my hopes on it.
我不得不说
So I must press the point...
既然擎天柱都相信霸天虎有投诚的潜质
if Optimus believes that even a Decepticon holds the potential for change
为什么汽车人就不会叛变呢？
why couldn't the reverse be true?
擎天柱在霸天虎阵营的那段时间里
No one truly knows what went on behind the Decepticon curtain
谁知道发生了什么？
while Optimus was off the grid?
你不了解 汽车人也不了解
Not you, not the Autobots.
关于这点 我百分之百的同意救护车所说的
I'm 100% with Ratchet on this one.
是否成为霸天虎需要做出选择 福勒探员
Being a Decepticon is a choice, Agent Fowler.
我绝不相信擎天柱会在有生之年做出这样的决定
one that I have a hard time believing Optimus would make at any point in his life.
奥利安・派克斯也许现在不知道自己是汽车人
Orion Pax may not currently be an Autobot up here
但我坚信在他的内心深处 绝不会放弃追逐理想
but I must believe he will never stop being one in here.
面对艰难的逆境和失忆
Against all odds, suffering amnesia
擎天柱仍然得以逃脱并且正面对抗威震天
Prime engineered his own escape to face down Megatron.
擎天柱会改变吗？
But is Prime capable of change?
你知道你的问题吗 擎天柱？
You know your problem, Optimus?
你是个如此高大 如此强壮的汽车人 却如此…优柔寡断
For such a big, strong bot, you're soft.
你没有抓住机会把威震天砸成废铁！
You didn't pound Megatron into scrap when you had the chance!
错失了那么多良机！
Many chances, in fact!
你可以用钻头把我杀掉
You might as well use your drill to finish me.
你还等什么？这是莫大的荣耀
What are you waiting for? Think of the glory?
机不可失 擎天柱会趁机动手的
Seize the day. Optimus would.
不 他不会
No, he wouldn't.
请告诉我擎天柱 你会放我一马吗？
So, tell me, Optimus, do you intend to take me alive
或是就此了结恩怨
or end this here and now?
擎天柱刚用实际行动证明
Prime has recently proven he's willing to go
为了保护人类他不惜付出任何代价
further than ever to protect humanity.
擎天柱是一个真正的爱国者
Optimus Prime is a true patriot.
他和他的团队冒着生命危险
He and his team continue to risk their lives
日以继夜
day in and day out
并且不求任何回报
asking absolutely nothing in return.
万一你牺牲了 擎天柱
If you don't survive, Optimus
恐怕这星球也活不成了
I fear neither will this planet.
那好吧
Very well.
简单明了地说
The simple fact is
擎天柱的身体里没有一块坏电路
Prime doesn't have a bad circuit in his body.
快走啊 死老头！
Move it, gramps!
福勒探员 有这个必要吗？
Agent Fowler, is that really necessary?
作为跟汽车人的联系人
As liaison to the Autobots
我极力警告你们
I strongly caution that
现在怀疑擎天柱的奉献精神 绝对不合时宜
now would be the worst time to call Prime's dedication into question.
我们可能要面临一个前所未有的威胁
We're on the verge of an even greater threat than we faced before.
霸天虎们正在寻找来自塞博特恩的远古遗物
The Decepticons are on the hunt for long-buried relics from Cybertron.
初步情报显示这些是拥有神秘力量的圣物
Preliminary intel suggests they could be sacred objects with mystical properties
或是大规模杀伤性武器
or weapons of mass destruction.
神秘力量？
Mystical?
啊 这一行也划掉！
Uh, strike that, too!
我的中心意思是 啊！
The point I'm trying to make here is... Agh!
等一等！擎天柱？我需要帮助
Hold on! Prime? I need an assist.
福勒探员 你发现机械党成员了吗？
Agent Fowler, have you uncovered M.E.C.H. agents?
没有 不是他们
No. They're okay.
布莱斯将军想要了解你的健康状况
General Bryce here just needs to confirm the state of your health and welfare.
我很好 布莱斯将军
I am fine, General Bryce.
你好吗？
How are you?
我很好 战士？
I'm well, uh, soldier.
比尔 我想现在我能作一份有足够说服力的报告
Bill... I believe I have everything I need to make a persuasive case
证明擎天柱还健康地活着
that Optimus Prime is, indeed, alive and well.
同时坚定不移地站在我们这边
And firmly on our side.
我们很感激您的支持 长官
We appreciate your support, sir.
准许离开！
Dismissed.